https://www.lasalle.edu/privacy

Website Privacy Notice
La Salle University > Website Privacy Notice
La Salle University respects your privacy.
La Salle University (“La Salle”) is committed to protecting personal privacy.  Information provided on the lasalle.edu domain will be used by La Salle in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.  Please read this privacy notice carefully so that you understand our privacy practices.
The Information We Gather Automatically
When you visit the lasalle.edu domain, or any lasalle.edu subdomains, certain information will be automatically collected by Google Analytics and aggregated to measure on site usage including geographic location of visitors and pathways navigated through the website. Your visit to the website, as well as device and browser information may be tracked through Google Analytics, but you will remain anonymous. Information gathered by way of Google Analytics does not identify you as an individual. You may opt out of this service by visiting Google’s opt-out page found here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
La Salle may also collect tracking information through the use of cookies, which place certain information on your device, or tracking pixels, a code embedded into the website, in order to facilitate your future access to and with our site, or to measure the effectiveness of La Salle’s marketing efforts. You may disable cookies through your browser settings. Be advised that disabling or deleting cookies may impact your ability to use certain features of the website.
The Information You Provide
We may also collect information from you in order to provide you with services or information about La Salle. The information collected in the “Request Info”, “Visit”, “Apply” or “Give” sections of the website will be used to send you postal mail or e-mail, or in some cases it may be used to contact you via phone (text or voice).  Additionally, the information gathered may be used for admissions-related purposes such as sending you information about enrollment if you self-identify as a prospective student, processing your application, scheduling and confirming a visit to La Salle, or to complete a gift to La Salle.
Third-Party Links
Our Website may contain links to other websites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy (“Third-Party Websites”). If you access Third-Party Websites using the links provided, the operators of such sites may collect information from you and use it in accordance with their own privacy policies, which may differ from ours. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those Third-Party Websites so that you understand if/how they collect and/or use information from you or your computer.
Special Notice for EU Residents (GDPR)
If you are located in a European Union Member State or the European Economic Area, La Salle acknowledges your rights and our obligations in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). La Salle will process personal or sensitive data (information) only as necessary in the exercise of its legitimate interests as a non-profit institution of higher learning guided through its mission. We may process information to recruit, register or enroll students at La Salle, to provide and administer housing, manage student accounts, provide academic support and advising, develop and deliver education programming, facilitate reporting, auditing and accreditation, as well as other processes and functions necessary for the administration of an institution of higher education. With respect to the information it processes, La Salle will employ reasonable and appropriate data protection measures, securing strictly monitored access.
La Salle will disclose your information to appropriate third parties only if we have your consent, if you have made the information public, if doing so is necessary to administer a contract you have with La Salle, if we are required by law, or if doing so will protect your interests and you are physically or legal incapable of providing consent.
You have the right to exercise any of your rights contemplated by Articles (15) through (22) of the GDPR, including the right of data access, data rectification, data erasure or “to be forgotten”, restricting the processing of data , data portability, or to object to the data held by us.
If you believe La Salle has not complied with the GDPR, you have the right to file a complaint with the appropriate Supervisory Authority in the European Union. Questions concerning this Policy can be addressed to La Salle’s Chief Information Officer, whom you can reach at:
LA SALLE UNIVERSITY
ATTN: KARL HORVATH (CHIEF INFORMATION OFFICER)
© Copyright 2020 La Salle University. All rights reserved. | Privacy
